不错嘛
Not so bad.
比外面看起来好
Better than look from outside.
别装酷了闺女 多完美的房间
Drop the cool girl acts. It's perfect.
我们家房子里居然有霉菌
So, it turns out our house has mold --
并不说明这位优秀主妇持家无方
Which is not a reflection on this excellent homemaker.
不管怎样 在清除霉菌期间
Anyway, we have to vacate the house
我们得搬出来
while it's being treated.
我订到了附近一间旅馆的最后一间房
I got us the last room at a hotel nearby.
五个人共享一间房
I was a little concerned about
让我有点担心
the five of us sharing a room.
不过就一个晚上 没准会很有意思呢
But for one night? I don't know, could be fun.
-看着点 -小心点
- Watch it! - Look out!
海莉 我需要有无线网的角落 下来
Haley, I need the wi-fi corner. Get down.
我需要instagram
Ugh, I need instagram
来知道这世界还是美好的
to know there's still beauty in the world!
卢克 你会把狗吵醒的
Luke, you'll set off the dogs!
瞧瞧我从大厅的自动贩卖机
Look what I got from the vending machine
买到一条查尔斯顿咀嚼糖
in the lobby -- a Charleston Chew.
还记得这个吗
Remember these?
有谁能叫那家尼日利亚人
Can someone please tell the Nigerian family
让他们的狗闭嘴吗
to shut their dogs up?!
看这个 根据包装所说
Check it out! According to this wrapper,
我们有机会赢取2005年全明星的门票
we can win tickets to the 2005 all-star game!
我最期待晚上的时光
I think I'm most excited about the night.
-会像露营一样的 -是啊
- It's gonna be like camping. - Yeah.
还有人要用洗手间吗
Okay, does anybody else need to use the bathroom?
不用了
No.
太好了 终于能躺下了
Great. Oh, finally.
我忘带牙套了
I forgot my night guard.
不好意思 妈
Sorry, Mom.
我在想什么 这不是我的书
What am I thinking? This isn't my book.
很好 既然都说到了
Great -- now that we talked about it,
我还是再去一次洗手间吧
I need to use the bathroom again.
问你们最后一遍的意义是什么
What is the point of a last call...
我要过来了
Coming through!
如果你们还是随心所欲
if you guys are just gonna do whatever -
今晚换人睡浴缸吧 比如海莉
Someone else sleep in the tub tonight. Like Haley.
好了 大家都躺下了 能不能
Okay, now that we're all here, can we just --
不是吧
No!
该死的火车又来了
It's that stupid train.
要把那条该死的狗吵醒了
It's gonna wake up those stupid dogs.
它们又要叫个没完没了
They're gonna start their stupid barking and --
它们没听到
They didn't hear it.
安静 所有人 不要说晚安了
Quiet, everybody. No "Good nights."
该死 雷·查普曼去世了
Son of a gun. Ray Chapman just died.
就是啊
I know!
他以前总给我留最好的骨头
He used to give me the best bonings.
你想的是我们的供肉商吧 雷·伊士曼
You're thinking of our butcher -- Ray Eastman.
希望是
I hope.
查普曼是我的一个海军朋友
No, Chapman was a navy buddy.
我一直想给他写信
I always meant to write to him.
杰 这太让人难过了
Oh, Jay, that's so sad.
我恨死他了
I hated his guts.
就像人家说的 做事不能总是拖延
It's like they say -- you cannot put these things off.
谢天谢地 曼尼回来了
Thanks god Manny's here.
每次他跟那个
I always get so nervous
大点的男孩萨姆一起出去 我都很紧张
when he goes out with that older boy, Sam.
我觉得我可以给他的寡妇发个信息
I guess I could try texting the widow.
他们每次都那样停在门前
They always stay in the driveway like that.
他们在干什么
What are they doing?
杰 去看看
Jay, go look.
歌洛莉亚 你不能去吗
Gloria, can't you do it?
不 我不能去
No, I can't do it because you know
因为他总说我管得太多了
that he always say that I am nosey.
曼尼最近的举止很可疑
And Manny's been acting very suspicious lately
我觉得是那个男孩的坏影响
I think that that older boy's a bad influence on him.
你能看到吗
Can you see?
看上去他开了一部野马
Looks like he's driving a Mustang.
车不错
Pretty sweet one, too.
-该死 -怎么了
- What the hell? - What?
他们在亲嘴
They're kissing.
萨姆是个女孩
Sam's a girl.
这反倒让你更吃惊吗
That gives a bigger reaction?
曼尼有女朋友了 他却没告诉我
Manny has a girlfriend, and he has not told me?
他来了
Here he comes,
先别急着拿问题轰炸他
and let's not ambush him with a bunch of questions.
不 他也许会想表现得酷一点
No. He's probably gonna want to play this pretty cool.
你们好啊
Oh, hey, guys.
我上去了
Well, heading up.
不 等等
No, wait!
晚上玩得怎么样
How was your night?
你知道的 年轻人的那些
Oh, you know, just teens being teens.
不管怎样 明天有大比赛 晚安
Anyway, big game tomorrow. Night.
曼尼的初恋女友是个开野马的高三女生
Manny's first girlfriend is a senior with a Mustang.
我还想赌是个有小胡子的大二生呢
I'd have put my money on a sophomore with a mustache.
你锯那块鸡排
You've been sawing
已经锯了十分钟了
at that chicken fried steak for 10 minutes.
叫点别的吃吧
Just order something else.
米奇尔 今天有比赛
Mitchell, it's game day.
我不能吃别的 这是我的幸运餐
I can't. It's my lucky meal.
天啊 管它呢
Oh, God. Here we go.
真是太有吸引力了
Well, that's attractive.
你看起来像只啃拖鞋的狗狗
You look like a puppy with a slipper.
在我的领导下 学校的橄榄球队
Under my leadership, the varsity football team
已经创造了5胜0负的令人兴奋的新纪录
is now 5-0 -- new school record, very exciting.
小卡 我在这里都能闻到你帽子的臭味
Cam, I can smell your hat from over here.
我能把它拿去洗了吗
Can I please just pop it in the laundry?
把幸运洗掉吗 我带着它去所有的比赛
And wash the luck off? I've worn it to every game.
他对体育一点都不了解
See, he knows nothing about sports.
所以我这回不难为他
That's why I've given him a pass.
他不需要去看比赛
He doesn't have to go to games.
但是 我会去的 听说很精彩
Although -- I-I do -- I hear it's fun.
在破木板上坐三个小时
Three hours on a splintery plank
旁边都是看到自家小孩弄残别人孩子
with parents squealing with delight
就发出兴奋尖叫的家长
as their children maim each other.
他来了就知道了 现在凳子都是铝制的
He'd know if he came. The seats are aluminum now.
好吧
Okay.
老板请你吃馅饼 教练
Some pie on the house, coach.
还有 那边那对夫妻帮你买了单
Oh, and that couple over there picked up your tab.
谢谢
Oh! Thank you.
至少我还能从这场疯狂里得到点补贴
At least I'm getting some perks out of all this craziness
不 他们只付了你那份
and -- nope, they just covered your part.
游泳池就在外面
Lot of pool out there.
要不要玩马可波罗游戏
How about some Marco Polo?
不要
Nah.
像旧时一样在水中嬉戏
Just like the old days, huh?
不
No.
不行
Not it!
老爸 真要这样吗
Dad! Really!
好一群爱抱怨的人啊
Bunch of complainers out here, huh?
亲爱的 我出去跑会儿步
Honey, I'm gonna go for a run,
-过会儿说不定能一起游个泳 -好的
- and then maybe after we go for a swim. - Okay.
那是什么
What's that?
一种香体喷雾 叫"性感炸弹"
It's a body spray called Sex Grenade.
旅馆里一个离婚男人推荐的
One of the divorced dads in the hotel recommended it.
这味道能把人搞疯
That smell is driving me crazy.
说明起作用了
Then it's working.
什么情况 卡住了
What the hell? It's stuck.
离我们远点
Get away from us!
没地方躲了
There's nowhere else to go!
我喘不过气来了
I can't breathe!
把门打开
Open the door!
这旅馆居然还有清洁服务吗
There's an actual maid service at this hotel?!
老爸 不要
Dad, no!
喷光了
It's empty.
没事了
We're okay, guys.
我去把这个丢掉
I'm gonna toss this.
发生了这种事情
When something like that happens,
真是令人深思
it makes you think, huh?
-卢克 -开什么玩笑
- Luke! - Seriously?!
克莱尔
Claire?
我不是
Nope.
我是说 我干什么呢
I mean, what am I doing?
我居然走错房间了
I am totally at the wrong room.
-真的吗 -对不起 菲尔
- Are you? - I'm sorry, Phil.
事情不是你想的那样
It's not what it looks like.
皱了的床 红酒...
Rumpled bed, wine...
胸罩
bra.
我就知道
I knew it!
你一个人睡觉了
You've been sleeping by yourself.
你怎么能这样
How could you?
对不起 我实在是受不了了
I am so sorry. I just couldn't take it anymore,
我需要一个地方 这是什么味道
and I needed a place where -- What is that smell?
背叛的味道
Betrayal.
在客厅举行家庭议会
Family meeting in the living room.
-我们不是已经 -快到客厅
- Aren't we already in -- - In the living room!
真不知道该怎么把这话说出口
There's no easy way to say this.
你们母亲要离开我们了
Your mother's leaving us.
她找到了另一个可以让她快乐的房间
She's found another room that makes her happy.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
听着 我需要一些空间
Okay, look, I needed a little space,
而正好那边有一个房间空出来了
and there was a room that opened up down the hall --
然后就一发不可收拾了
Then one thing led to another.
你走吧 克莱尔
Spare us, Claire.
慢着 老妈在别的房间睡觉吗
So, wait. Mom's staying in that other room?
你可以在周末拜访她
You can visit her on the weekends.
我们不是再待一天就可以了吗
Aren't we here for just one more day?
我就知道你会最先发火
I knew you'd be the one to lash out.
如果老妈要住在空房间
If Mom is staying in an empty room,
我们何不让几个人过去跟她住
why can't some of us stay with her?
你高兴了吧 克莱尔
You happy, Claire?
你拆散了整个家庭
You're breaking up the family.
不 孩子们 爸爸说得对
No, guys, your father is right.
都是我的错
This is my fault.
我还是回我的房间
I should go back to my room
好好反省我的过错吧
and just think about what I've done.
别这样 我们恨死这里了
Come on. We hate it here.
我多一秒都不想
I cannot look at that red hair
再瞧见浴室排水槽里的红发了
in the shower drain one more second.
睁大眼睛瞧瞧 我们几个没人是红头发
Look around here, people. None of us have red hair.
好吧 你们其中一人得跟妈妈走
Okay, one of you has to go with your mom,
我们用民主的方法来决定
so we'll do this the democratic way.
谁抽到了最短的披萨边
Whoever pulls the short crust --
-别呀 老爸 -我不想抽签
- Come on, Dad. - No, I don't want to do that.
好吧
Fine!
如果你们都想走 就走吧
You all want to go, then go.
背叛自己的亲生父亲
Turn your back on your father,
不需要你们
just spare me
-虚情假意的道歉和鳄鱼... -好
- the empty apologies and the crocodile... -Okay.
-终于可以走了 -...泪
- Finally. - tears.
我不睡浴缸
I call "No bathtub."
又是个好运礼物篮 大爸
Another good-luck gift basket, Daddy.
他们居然让七岁小孩签收
Oh, they just let 7-year-olds sign for these. Okay.
不错呀
How nice!
来看看里面有什么
Let's see what we've got here.
茄子果冻
Eggplant jelly?
难以想象他们不喜欢你的话
What do they send if they
会送什么鬼东西
don't like you?
教练加油 海豚队加油
"Go coach, go Dolphins!"
看上去"加油"加得有点过
I don't know. It seems a little "Go" heavy.
粉红盐
Pink salt?
人们现在都是什么毛病
What is wrong with people?
我得赶紧走了
Okay, I got to skedaddle.
比赛结束后再见
I'll see you guys after the big game.
好的 再见
All right, then.
-这还没完 因为 -忘拿钥匙了
- And we're waiting because... - Forgot my keys.
是的 在那里
Yes, you did. Right over there.
-每次都要这样 -是的 每一次
- Every time. - Yes, every time.
我们第一次赢球那天我就忘拿了
I forgot them on the day of our first win,
这招屡试不爽
and it's worked ever since.
往左边挪一下
Now scooch to the left.
我不能让你再搞那个咖啡桌的把戏了
I'm not letting you do the coffee-table thing again.
米奇尔 迷信是体育的重要组成部分
Mitchell, superstitions are a big part of sports.
同样也是巫术和邪教以及巫毒术的一部分
And witchcraft and cults and voodoo, but --
听我说 你知道吗
Hey, look, you know what?
我没逼你喜欢橄榄球
I'm not asking you to like football,
可我喜欢橄榄球
but I like football.
在我的成长过程中 橄榄球是我的一切
Football was everything to me growing up.
我原来只是个农场胖基佬
I was just a big, gay farm kid
可当我加入橄榄球队以后我终于被接受了
until I joined the football team and I finally fit in.
我不期望你会喜欢
Now, I don't expect you to like it.
我不期望你会来看比赛
I don't expect you to come to the games.
但我期望你能表现得不那么傲慢
But I do expect you to be 5% less condescending.
给我让开
Now scooch.
加油 海豚队
Go, Dolphins!
太过头了 车钥匙 咖啡桌
It's too much -- the car keys, the coffee table,
你放在正门口的滑板
your roller skate on the front porch.
这里面有巧克力吗
I-is there any chocolate in any of these?
你得从这罐番茄干上刮下来
You'll have to scrape it off this sun-dried tomato.
我觉得某种意义上
I suppose on some level,
他说的可能有道理
it's possible that he might have a point.
我不喜欢体育 真的
I hate sports. I do.
可如果你是我爸用他的教育方式带大的
But if you had my dad and my upbringing...
你有玩游戏最后才被选的经历吗 莉莉
I mean, have you ever been picked last for a team, Lily?
那天在体育馆 那些坏女孩...
Well, at gym the other day, these mean girls --
你肯定没体会过 成天被欺负和嘲笑
I mean, you have no idea, Lily, the bullying and the teasing.
她们把我放到了球袋里
They put me in the ball bag.
如果我真的表现得很傲慢
If I am a little dismissive,
只是因为我悲惨的身世
it's only because of my harrowing backstory.
她们说我敢告诉别人就杀了你和大爸
They said if I told, they would kill you and daddy.
我的天
Oh, my god.
我一直在考虑自己
I've -- I've been making this all about myself.
一点都没为小卡着想
I haven't even been thinking about Cam.
这都什么事啊
This is crazy.
就是 都什么事啊
Yes, this is crazy.
谁关心我爱不爱橄榄球啊
Who cares if I like football?
大爸喜欢
Daddy likes football,
我爱大爸 所以 我要告诉他
and I like daddy, so -- I need to tell him.
告诉他我会更支持他
I need to tell him I'm gonna be more supportive,
还要 亲爱的 你在帮我打给他吗
and I need to -- oh, honey, are you calling him for me?
对 我要投诉
Yes, I have a complaint.
我想找哈利或戴维
Can I please talk to Harry or David?
什么味道
What's that smell?
你说的应该是我奔放的新香水吧
I believe you're referring to my bold new scent --
"性感炸弹"
"Sex gre-nod."
是不是为萨姆喷的 那个名字
Is that for Sam, your friend that is a girl,
像男生的女生朋友
but has the name of a boy?
我知道你昨晚在偷看我
I knew you were spying on me last night.
对 我有女朋友了
Yes, I have a girlfriend.
我就直说了 省得你去打听
Let me save you some snooping.
她聪明 漂亮 读高三
She's smart. She's pretty. She's a senior.
是我们学校的交际花
She's our high school's "It" Girl,
此花为了我甩了篮球队长
and "It" Dumped the captain of the basketball team for me.
你才十五岁 就跟高三的约会了
So, you're only 15, and you go out with the senior.
你真想来这套吗
Are you sure you want to play that game?
你想吗
Are you?
我只是想
I just want to --
妈 你管太多了
Mom, you're butting in.
我只想见见她
I just want to meet her.
绝对不行
Oh, absolutely not.
还太早
It's way too early.
能不能保证在我准备好之前都别过问这事
Promise me you'll stay out of this until I'm ready.
这是最接近"好"的答案了
That's as close as you're gonna get to a "Yes."
好了 我要去收拾了
Okay, I got to go get ready.
萨姆会来接我 在赛前吃点东西
Sam's gonna pick me up for a bite before the game.
杰 我不喜欢
Jay, I don't like this.
虽然不是我最喜欢的退场方式
Eh, it's not my favorite exit of his,
不过比鞠躬谢幕好多了
but it beats the dramatic stage bow.
不是说这个 那女生比他成熟太多了
No, that girl is too advanced for him.
我不希望她强迫曼尼
I don't want her to force him
做他不想做的事
to do anything that he doesn't want to.
我倒觉得不论那女孩想做什么他都能应付
I think he'll be okay with whatever she wants to do.
你快去 我不能插手
Okay, you go because I cannot butt in.
你可以去跟她说
Maybe you can talk to her.
吓唬她一下 把她镇住
Maybe you can put the fear of God into her!
怎样 砸碎她的挡风玻璃
What, bust her windshield?
扭断小指吗
Break her pinkie?
我这就去把监控关了
I go disconnect the security camera.
车不错啊
Nice ride.
谢谢
Thanks.
其实 曼尼并不习惯
You know, Manny's not really used to...
坐快车
fast cars.
我不知道你开着这辆野马
And I don't know what your intentions are
到底想干什么 不过
with this Mustang, but, um,
我建议你凡事都要慢慢来
I suggest you take things nice and slow.
明白了吗
We clear?
听起来你是想让我开慢点
Um, sounds like you really want me to drive slow.
不是 我想说的是
No, uh, what I think I'm saying is,
用手就好了
hands can do things.
不对 等下
No, uh, hang on.
年轻人有欲望很正常
Young people have urges, which is only natural.
我也有
I also have urges.
好吧
Okay.
我是说 你够十八岁了
I mean, the point is, you're 18.
我盯着你呢[看上你了]
And I have my eye on you.
杰 你在干什么
Jay, what are you doing?
回屋去
Go inside.
说了不插手的
No means no!
冲
Run!
得分
Score!
赢了
Win!
太棒了
Yes!
第二节只剩四分钟
And with 4 minutes left in the second quarter...
海豚队27分
...that's Dolphins -- 27...
獾队 零分
...Badgers -- nothing.
漂亮 打得真精彩
All right! What a game!
我们的队员就像是
Our guys were playing like
穷人家孩子在和富二代们打比赛似的
they come from a much poorer neighborhood.
你不觉得奇怪吗
You don't think it's funny
都没见到那女生 萨姆
that we haven't seen that girl, Sam,
取个男生名的那个
the one named for a boy?
这比赛这么重要
I mean, it's a big game.
她如果真是曼尼的女朋友 就该
If she was really his girlfriend, she --
歌洛莉亚 现实点吧
Gloria, be realistic.
你想她怎样
What do you want,
站在第一排
her standing in the first row
举个写着"曼尼加油"的牌子吗
with a sign saying "Go, Manny"?
-我只是说 -她就是这么做的
- I'm just saying that... - 'Cause that's what she's doing.
那是她吗
That's her?
还挺漂亮的嘛
She's pretty.
那牌子是她做的吗
She made that sign for him?
跟你说了她是个不错的女孩
I told you, she's a great girl.
你看 她还用了荧光粉
And look -- she used glitter,
真有一套
for god's sakes.
杰 我觉得她真的很喜欢曼尼 看
Jay, I think that she really likes him. Look.
她望着曼尼的眼神跟我看曼尼的眼神一样
She looks at him the same way that I look at him.
好甜蜜
So sweet.
但她有这种眼神是正常的
And in her case, healthy.
加油 海豚队
Go, Dolphins!
今晚我们队球迷的门票钱
We're really giving our fans
花得真值 孩子们
their money's worth tonight, boys.
他来了
He came.
他跑到了30码线 20码
He's at the 30, at the 20,
10码 入禁区了 触地得分
the 10, and he's in for a touchdown.
-獾队得分 -什么
- Badgers score. - What?!
我们一整年都没被人那样反击过
We haven't let anyone run back a kick all year.
怎么回事
What happened?
快跑 拦截
Run! Tackle!
给我上
Try!
獾队触地得分
Touchdown, Badgers.
到底怎么回事 教练
What's going on, coach?
大家忽然都不在状态
All of a sudden, everyone's just off.
对
Yep.
不过米奇尔终于来看比赛了
At least Mitchell finally made it to a game.
对
Yep.
注意力集中 防守的
Focus, defense.
他们队有两个人防着我们
They got two players hurting us.
两个人有那么难防吗
It's not that much to keep track of!
该死 忘放芥末酱了
Shoot. Mustard.
我不能告诉曼尼 他会难过死的
I couldn't tell Manny because it would kill him,
也不能告诉歌洛莉亚
and I couldn't tell Gloria
她气急了我会死的
because she would kill me.
好好的热狗就这么给毁了
Hell of a way to ruin a nice hot dog.
第三节结束 双方打成平手
End of the third quarter, and we're all tied up.
塔克教练
Coach Tucker!
大家都过来喝点水
Okay, hey, everybody, grab a cup of water.
水杯你们还能拿得住吧
Maybe you could hold on to those, huh?
多精彩啊
How exciting is this, huh?
你的记事版掉了
Oh, you dropped your little clipboard.
我以为你今晚有应酬
I thought you had a work dinner tonight.
是的 不过我推掉了
I did, but I blew them off.
我更想到这来支持你的球队
I'd rather be here supporting the team.
加油 海豚队
You better go, Dolphins!
是啊 真好 不过比赛快结束了
Yeah, love that, but, you know, the game's almost over.
要是不想赶上堵车的话 就...
You might want to beat traffic, so...
我以为我来观赛你会高兴
I thought you'd be happy that I was here.
可我怎么觉得你急着想摆脱我
Why do I feel like you're trying to get rid of me?
我也不知道 我没说你是扫把星
I have no idea. It's not because you're a jinx.
扫把星 你认为我是扫把星吗
A jinx? Do you think I'm a jinx?
不 不不不不不
No! No, no, no, no, no.
这不会都是你的错
This all can't be on you.
可我觉得听起来
I'm hearing a lot of things
跟你嘴上说的刚好相反
that sound like the opposite of what you're --
教练 我们需要你部署战略
Hey, coach! We need a play.
还有马尔科姆刚刚被蜜蜂蜇了
And Malcolm just got stung by a bee.
我得走了 怎么会有蜜蜂
I got to go. A bee?!
快去弄点小苏打来
Okay, get some baking soda.
你们知道酒吧在哪吗
Hey, do you guys know where the bar is?
这里就是 老兄
You're here, my friend.
想来点什么
What are you in the mood for?
我想让妻子和孩子们回来
Well, I'd like my wife and kids back,
但先来杯夏敦埃酒好了
but I'd take a chardonnay.
看你表情就知道没什么好事
Ah, I thought you had that look about you.
我是莱斯特 这位是卡尔
I'm Lester. This is Carl.
-你好 卡尔 -你好
- Hey, Carl. - Hey.
我知道你现在很伤心 不过
I know it hurts now, but, uh,
作一个花花公子
being a man-about-town,
独来独往 将会有意外的惊喜
on your own, has its perks.
这杯算我请你的
This is on me.
谁离开谁的
Ah. So, who left who?
她离开我的
She did.
她说需要空间
She said she needed some space,
自己找了间房 把孩子们带走了
got her own place, and took the kids.
别灰心 老兄
Chin up, my friend.
更多的精彩在等待着你
Adventure awaits.
卡尔 能帮我刷一下卡吗
Carl, could you swipe me?
玉米片机把我的卡吞了
Nacho machine ate my card.
菲尔
Phil.
你好 阿尤拉 这是我的邻居
Hey, Ayoola. This is my neighbor here.
-去泳池吗 -不去了 谢谢
- Pool? - Oh, no, thanks.
-现在没有那个心情 -好吧
- I don't think I'd be much fun right now. - Okay.
菲尔 老兄
Phil, buddy,
接到这样的邀请 就应该赶紧上啊
you get an offer like that, you got to jump on it,
就算只是一夜风流也好
even if it's just a one-time thing.
我不知道 她人不错 孩子也挺可爱
I don't know -- she's nice, her kids seem great,
但我都不会说她的语言
but I don't even speak her language.
谁让你跟她说话了
Who said anything about speaking?
我想你们俩误会了
I think you guys have got the wrong idea.
我妻子明天会回来的
My wife's getting back tomorrow.
她当然会回来 小冠军
Oh, of course she is, champ.
我只是想说 生命苦短
Uh, I'm just saying, life is short,
找点无伤大雅的乐子又有何妨
and why deny yourself a little innocent fun?
你妻子她就没顾忌那么多
Your wife certainly hasn't.
我觉得自己还没准备好
I'm not sure I'm up for it.
好吧 但不要让好生活等太久 菲尔
Okay, but don't wait too long to start living life, Phil.
多谢 伙计们
Thanks, guys.
知道吗 当你不去想
You know when you don't think about
在你之前谁曾进过这里
who was in there before you,
在旅馆浴缸泡澡其实很让人放松
a hotel bath can be really quite relaxing.
艾丽克斯收到我的信息了吗
Do you know if Alex got my text?
给你刷卡买的酒
Your swipe-card wine.
谢谢
Thank you.
刚才我在大厅里
Hey, so, I was talking
跟那几个苦闷男人聊天
to those sad guys that are in the lobby,
他们说旅馆这周半数房间都空着
and they said the hotel's been half-empty all week.
是半数房间住满了 宝贝儿
Half-full, honey.
生活中要保持乐观的态度
Be positive for once in your life.
好的 但这不是我想表达的意思
Okay, not quite the point I was making.
我很想听你表达你的意思 不过现在
I want to hear your point, but right now,
这杯神奇的果汁会让妈妈
this magic juice is gonna help mama
在浴缸里体验池滨酒吧的乐趣
turn that bathtub into a swim-up bar.
我要说的是 我们从一开始就可以
I'm just saying we could have been
-开两间房分开住 -好吧
- in two hotel rooms this entire time. - Okay.
等等
Wait.
你是说爸爸让我们无缘无故遭了这么多罪
So, dad put us through hell for nothing?
你们听见了吗
Do you guys hear that?
我的英雄从圣坛上掉下的声音吗
The sound of my hero falling off his pedestal?
不是
Uh, no.
你的英雄在泳池
The sound of your hero
和那些尼日利亚人嬉戏的声音
playing with the Nigerians in the pool.
好了 当我说"马可"时
Okay, so, when I say "Marco" --
-你好 马可 -不不 我是菲尔
- Hi, Marco. - No, no, I'm Phil.
我要说的是"马可" 然后
I'm gonna say "Marco" and then --
你好 菲尔
Hi, Phil.
我们重新再来
Let's take it from the top.
我要闭上我的眼睛
I'm gonna close my eyes.
不不不 不是你 阿尤拉
No, no, not -- not you, Ayoola.
你睁着眼睛就好
You keep your eyes open.
-你能睁开... -马可
- Can you open... - Marco!
不 易亚卜 不要离开泳池
No, uh, Iyapo, can you stay in the pool?
-这样当我说"马可" -你好马可
- That way, when I say "Marco" - Hi, Marco.
天哪
Come on.
整个房间都是他的 他却在干这个吗
He has a room to himself, and that's what he's doing?
我们应该感到惊讶吗
How surprised should we be?
他基本上就是个极度活跃的小孩子
I mean, he's basically a hyperactive toddler
整天都想着玩儿
that just wants to play all the time.
没错
Yeah.
但其实他真正想要的
Although it's really more about
是和我们在一起
wanting to spend time with us.
这基本上是爸爸的全部心愿
It's kind of all dad ever wants.
你说得对
That's true.
他就好像 总喜欢缠着我们
He's, like, obsessed with us.
你们觉得他骗我们旅馆客满了
Do you think he lied about the hotel being booked
是为了能和我们待在一起吗
just so we'd all have to spend time together?
可我们却抛弃了他
And we totally ditched him.
他甚至为了我们扑到那瓶性感炸弹香水上
Even after he jumped on that sex grenade for us.
手太滑了 酒撒到浴缸里了
Butterfingers. I spilled my wine in the tub.
能再给我来一杯吗 宝贝儿
Would you mind, sweetie?
怎么了
What?
还剩6秒钟
Only 6 seconds left.
海豚队还落后三分
The dolphins still down by 3.
短短40码 长长的6秒
40 short yards, 6 long seconds.
我们可以的
We've got this.
数到三一起来"加油 海豚"
On three, "Go, dolphins."
二三 加油 海豚
Two, three go, dolphins!
好了 曼尼 只求上天保佑了
All right, Manny, this is a real hail mary.
无论输赢 我依然有个漂亮女友
Win or lose, I still have a hot girlfriend.
海豚队来到场边
Dolphins come to the line.
断球了
There's the snap.
汤米·帕克回传
Tommy Park back to pass.
-他看到前场 -快传
- He looks downfield. - Hit it.
-快传快传 -传给了接球手
- Hit it! Hit it! - He's got a receiver.
海豚队触地得分
Touchdown, dolphins!
我们赢了 米奇尔 我们赢了
We won! Mitchell, we won!
不要
Oh, no!
-喂 -米奇尔 我们赢了
- Hello? - Mitchell, we won!
我回头看 你不在了
And I looked back, and you weren't there!
请别生我的气
Please don't be mad at me.
我在栅栏上[持观望态度]
I'm on the fence.
我不怪你
I don't blame you.
我真傻 让你感觉这一切是你的错
I feel stupid for making you think this was all your fault.
不 我在栅栏上
No! I'm on the fence.
看你右边
Look to your right.
我想离开
I was trying to leave,
结果被卡住了
and then I got stuck on this fence With --
我的裤腿
my -- my pant leg is --
你在想什么呢
What were you thinking?
我们都知道你不擅长攀爬
We both know you're not a good climber.
我知道
Well, I know that.
那边就有停车场
There's a parking lot right over there.
我把车停这里了
I'm parked over here.
稳住 稳住
Sit right -- sit right -- sit right there.
稳住了
Sit right there.
-好了 放我下来 -二 三
- Okay, okay, put me down. - Two, three.
你不用把我扔出去吧
You don't have to throw me.
我明白你为什么不想让我来这里
Look, I -- I get why you don't want me here.
我知道不存在什么噩运
I-I know there's no such thing as bad luck,
但是存在负能量
But there -- there is bad energy,
我给你的体育世界带去了不少负能量
And I bring a lot of that to your whole sports world.
那是因为我和体育有段纠结的过去
And that's -- that's because of my own history with it
我应该做得更好才对
and you deserve better.
你已经最好了 知道吗
I couldn't do better. You know what?
咱们何不把体育看作是朋友当中
Why can't we look at sports like one of those friends
你们二人一个喜欢一个讨厌的那种
that one of us likes and the other doesn't?
体育就像你妈妈
Sports can be like your mom.
其实吧 我不讨厌这个
You know, actually, I-I didn't hate this.
-少来了 -不 我不讨厌
- Oh, shut up. - No, I didn't.
我有些领略到橄榄球文化了
I-I was kind of getting into the whole football culture.
其中有种高雅
There is an elegance that this has --
不
No!
不 这可是骆马毛的
No! This is vicuna!
你们这些原始人
You neanderthals!
精彩的比赛 冠军
Great game, champ.
谢谢
Thanks.
你还好吗
You okay?
只是有些累了
Yeah, just a little tired.
今天很累 晚安
It was a big day. Good night.
晚安 孩子
Night, kid.
稍等
Hey, wait a second.
你们队刚刚连赢六场
Your team just won six straight.
咱们用威士忌来庆祝下
Let's celebrate with a little scotch.
你已经大到可以抿第一口了
You're old enough for your first sip.
她甩了我 杰
She dumped me, Jay.
咱们来说说
Okay, we're gonna do this.
她只是利用我让她年长的男友嫉妒
She was just using me to make her old boyfriend jealous.
现在他们复合了
Now they're back together.
不要告诉妈妈 好吗
Don't tell mom, okay?
我感觉到她不喜欢萨姆
I had a sense she didn't like Sam.
是吗 她什么也没说
Really? She didn't say anything.
我的初恋女友
My first girlfriend.
她好完美
She was perfect.
屁股有点大
Eh, a little wide in the can.
-杰 -对不起
- Jay. - I'm sorry. Just...
要我说 你很幸运
You ask me, you're lucky.
她发短信甩我的
She dumped me by text
当时还在和她年长的男友热吻
while making out with her old boyfriend.
我崩溃哭泣 炭笔条花得跟睫毛膏一样
I broke down crying. My charcoal ran like mascara.
来得靠另一队的吉利物安慰我来着
I had to be comforted by the other team's mascot.
-这是幸运吗 -好好想想
- Lucky? - Think about it.
你这个年纪有多少男生
How many guys your age would kill
愿意付出一切让萨姆利用
to be used by a girl like Sam?
她选了你
She picked you.
她利用了你
She used you.
我就是个泄欲工具 杰
I was a body, Jay.
拜托 如果她选了个普通男生
Come on. If she had picked an average guy,
那个男友根本不会嫉妒
that boyfriend never would have got jealous.
她得选一个和那个男友一个水平的
She had to pick a guy on his level.
是 可能吧
Yeah. Maybe.
我不会骗你
Oh, I'm not gonna lie to you.
这很糟糕 有时候糟糕的感觉
It sucks, and sometimes
还会持续一阵子
it's got to suck for a while.
我真希望我可以说出什么咒语
I just wish I could say some magic words
或是拥抱你 就让这感觉烟消云散
or give you a hug -- make it all go away.
你说我可以抿一口威士忌 还算话吗
Can I still have a sip of that scotch like you said?
我刚开了一瓶
Okay, I just opened a bottle,
18年[岁]陈酿
A beautiful 18-year-old,
味道醇厚[身材好]
full-bodied.
萨姆
Sam!
好啦 好啦
Okay. Okay.
马可
Marco!
波罗
Polo?
马可
Marco!
波罗 波罗 波罗
Polo! Polo! Polo!
大半夜的谁会按门铃啊
Who rings the bell in the middle of the night?
真令人毛骨悚然
It is the creepiest thing.
我不知道 我肯定只是
I'm sure it's just, I don't know,
某人车坏了 想借我家电话
Some guy's car broke down and he wants to use our phone.
你没看过恐怖片吗
Have you ever seen a movie?
你还记得你们离开旅馆房间时
Okay, do you remember how sad I was
我有多伤心吗
when you guys left the hotel room?
菲尔 门外是什么人
Phil, what is on the other side of that door?
-你好 马可 -各位好
- Hi, Marco. - Hey, guys.
我说"你们应该来我家玩"
It's possible they misunderstood me
他们有可能误会了
when I said, "You guys should stop by."
你们应该来我家玩
Yeah, "You guys should stop by."
马可
Marco!
这下可好
All right.
什么情况
What is happening?!